Cooper there's no point using your fuel to chase...
Analyze the Endurance's spin.
Cooper what are you doing?
Docking.
Endurance's rotation is 67, 68 RPM.
Ok, get ready to match our spin with the retro thrusters.
It's not possible.
No, it's necessary.
Endurance is hitting stratosphere.
She's got no heat shield.
CASE you ready?
Ready!
Cooper this is no time for caution!
CASE if I black out you take the stick.
TARS you ready to engage the docking mechanism?
Endurance is starting to heat.
20 feet up.
10 feet up.
Cooper we are... lined up.
Initiating spin.
Come on TARS.
We are locked.
Easen up!
Easy.
Retro thrusters.
Main engines on.
Pushing out of orbit.
Come on baby.
Killing main engines.
Ok, we're out of orbit.